Jakarta, August 11, 2014

To. Timas Suplindo, PT

Att. HRD Department

Dear Madam,

My name is Rommy Zamanuddin, I am Thirty years old. I am graduated from PKN LPKIA of Bandung, majoring in Informatics Engineer with GPA 3.10. I am currently studying in STMIK Jayakarta majoring Information System. As experienced software programmer, I have designed and developed many software to

users.

At present I able to develop application with C# / Visual Basic language and database connectivity to SQL Server/MySQL. Beside that, I am considered energetic, motivated, honest, loyal, team player, and also a fast learner.

Thank you for your consideration. I look forward to hearing from you soon.

Yours Sincerely,

ROMMY ZAMANUDDIN

Enclosed:

- 1. Photograph
- 2. CV

ROMMY ZAMANUDDIN

1. Kramat Lontar 10 Blok J-44 Kel. Paseban Jakarta

2. Komp. Sukamenak Indah Blok G-18 Bandung, 40228 0813 2154 1294 0857 9344 5020 rzamanuddin@gmail.com

PERSONAL DATA

Marital status : Single

Place, Date of Birth : Bandung, August 15, 1984

Gender : Male

Religion : Moslem
Citizenship : Indonesia

Weight : 68 Kg.
Height : 175 Cm.



WORK EXPERIENCE

PT ASURANSI JIWA TUGU MANDIRI

Industry : Insurance
Location : Jakarta
Job Type : Permanent

Job Position : IT Programmer

Job Description : Develop and Maintain Information System for internal company,

Work Period : May 2012 - Current

Salary : Rp. 6.500.000

Allowances : Medical Insurance, Communication Allowance, Jamsostek, THR, Annual Bonus,

Leave Allowance. Pension Allowance.

PT AKHDANI REKA SOLUSI

Industry : IT Consultant

Location : Bandung

Job Type : Permanent

Job Position : Programmer

Job Description : Develop Software based on project

Work Period : January 2011 – April 2012 (1 Year 3 Month)

Salary : Rp. 2.500.000

Allowances : Medical Insurance, Bonus Project, THR

PT BERLEI INDONESIA

Industry : Garment Manufacture

Location : Cikarang

Job Type : Permanent

Job Position : Programmer

Job Description : Develop ERP for all department in company internal.

Work Period : October 2007 – January 2011 (3 Year 3 Month)

Salary : Rp. 2.735.000

Allowances : Medical, Jamsostek, THR

EDUCATION

Strata 1

Major : Information System
University : STMIK Jayakarta
Year : 2013 - Current

Location : Jakarta

Diploma III

Major : Informatics Engineer

University : Lembaga Pendidikan Komputer Indonesia Amerika

GPA : 3.10

Graduate Date : 8 October 2005

Location : Bandung

COURSES

NO	Course / Training	Location	Duration	Years
1	Merakit PC & Instalasi Linux Fedora Core2	Bandung	1 Days	2005
2	Micro Controller	Bandung	2 Days	2005
3	Subnetting IP	Bandung	2 Days	2005
4	Basic Of Wireless Networking	Bandung	2 Days	2005

SKILLS

Programming : C#, Visual Studio 2010/2008, ASP.NET Web Forms, Visual Basic 6.0.

Database : SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB, Ms. Access

Software : Crystal Report, FyiReporting, Microsoft Report, Ms. Office, Corel Draw.

Operating Systems : Ms. Windows, Linux Languages : Indonesian, English

Others : Entity Framework, Ajax, JQuery, CSS, HTML, Component One, ITextSharp,

QiosDev.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Company Internal Information System

Develop Information system used in internal company for support FA, Cash Management and marketing department.

Project Name : Sales Illustration (Desktop Based),

Sistem Informasi Keuangan & Akuntansi (SIKA) (Web Based)

Treasury Management System (Web Based)

Sistem Proteksi Kesehatan untuk PTPN X (WebProkes) (Web Based)
Sistem Administrasi Asuransi Jiwa Kumpulan (SAAJAK) (Web Based)

Year : 2012

Position : Programmer

Location : Jakarta

Development Tools : C#, Visual Studio 2010, ASP.NET Web Forms, Entity Framework, Ajax, Jquery,

VB 6, SQL Server 2008, Crystal Report 13.

Sistem Informasi Jaminan Kredit Bank (SIJKB)

Information system to facilitate Account Officer for manage customer, credit, mortgag, and document data.

Furthermore, this software provide a reminder facility for document that has expired or wil expire.

Year : 2012

Position : Programmer

Location : Bandung

Development Tools : C#, Visual Studio 2010, SQL Server 2008 CE, MongoDB, QIOS DevSuite

Call Center Reporting System

Reporting system for call center system to provide call activity data history.

Year : 2011 - 2012
Position : Programmer

Location : Jakarta

Development Tools : C#, Visual Studio 2010, FyiReporting, PostgreSQL 9.1

Sistem Informasi Sekolah (SIKOLAH)

Information system for school to manage student registration, mutation, attendance, grade, guestion etc.

Year : 2011

Position : Team Leader & Programmer

Location : Bandung

Development Tools : C#, Visual Studio 2010, MySQL, SQL Server 2008 CE,

FyiReporting 4.1, ITextSharp.

Berlei Management System (BMS)

ERP Application System used for internal company for all department such as Packing, Engineering, Finance,

Purchasing, Trimstore etc.

Year : 2007 - 2011
Position : Programmer

Job Description : Develop ERP for internal company.

Location : Cikarang.

Development Tools : Visual Basic 6.0, SQL Server 2000, Ms. Access 2000,

Component One 8, Crystal Report 8.5, Ms. Excel 2003.

EXPECTED SALARY

Amount : Rp. 9.500.000,00

Note: All supporting documents and references are available upon request.